Arsenii Ashukha

Moscow, Russia • 🔊 +7-965-178-2915 • ⋈ ars.ashuha@gmail.com • ars-ashuha.ru



Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT, I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT/MSU/HSE I work as a teacher assistant for some Machine Learning courses.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Hive, Linux, English (B2)

Education

2015 - 2017 Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: ?/5.0 Thesis Regularization of Deep Neural Nets, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT)



2015 - 2016 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0 Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian ML, Deep Learning, Machine Learning Result



2011 - 2015 Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Thesis Identification of unique kernels in topic models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU)



Teaching

- 2016 Now: Practical Lecture, University Course at MIPT, Machine Learning (parts 1,2), course page (RU)
- 2016 Now: Lecture / Practical Lecture, Additional Course at MIPT, Machine Learning in Action, course page (RU)
- 2016 Now: Practical Lecture, University Course at MSU/HSE, Deep Learning, course pages: MSU (RU), HSE (RU)

Experience

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

3 month

Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group (E. Krofto)

• Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN



Dec 2013 - Feb 2016

2 year 1 month p/t

Rambler, Moscow — R&D Engineer at ML Group (A. Gorokhov, P. Klemenkov)

- Improving the quality of classification users using browser history
- Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru
- Optimization performance of users classification
- Application of topic models to building users features

RAMBLER&Co

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013 3 month

Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group (M. Karpenko)

• Users query classification to show a mixing in search results

RAMBLER&Co

Publications

Dmitry Molchanov, Arseniv Ashuha and Dmitry Vetrov

- Dropout-based Automatic Relevance Determination Bayesian Deep Learning Workshop, Neural Information Processing Systems 2016
 - Arseniy Ashuha and Natalia Loukachevitch
- Bigram Anchor Words Topic Model International Conference on Image Analysis, Social Networks and Texts 2016